Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 3: Appropriations
  - Subseries 3.4: Appropriations, Interior; 1946-1964
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 1825-1827)
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 1828)
    - Legislation, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1829)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1830)
    - General (includes correspondence and legislation), 1951-1964 (Box 30, Folder 1831-1835)
  - Subseries 3.5: Appropriations, Legislative Branch and Public Works, 1949-1964
    - Legislative Branch, 1949-1964
      - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1836)
      - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1837)
      - Legislation, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1838)
      - Legislation, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1839)
    - General (includes correspondence and printed material), 1949-1954 (Box 30, Folder 1840-1841)
    - General (includes correspondence and printed material), 1949-1954 (continued) (Box 31, Folder 1842-1844)
    - General (includes correspondence and printed material), 1957-1963 (Box 31, Folder 1845-1849)
    - General (includes correspondence and printed material), 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1850-1852)
    - Public Works, 1958-1964
      - General (includes correspondence and printed material, 1958-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1853-1858)
  - Subseries 3.6: Appropriations, Miscellaneous, 1947-1965
    - Miscellaneous (includes correspondence and printed material), 1947-1965
      - 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 1859-1863)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 32, Folder 1864-1868)
      - 1952-1954 (Box 32, Folder 1869-1871)
      - 1952-1954 (continued) (Box 33, Folder 1872-1874)
      - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 1875)
      - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 1876)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 33, Folder 1877-1879)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1958 (continued) (Box 34, Folder 1880-1881)
      - 1958-1961 (Box 34, Folder 1882-1887)
      - 1962-1965 (Box 35, Folder 1888-1892)
- Series 4: Departmental, 1943-1964
  - Agriculture Adjustment Agency, general, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1893)
  - Subsidies (chiefly correspondence), 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 1894-1899)
  - Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1956-1964 (Box 35, Folder 1900-1903)
  - Armed Forces: Army, 1943-1947
    - Pearl Harbor correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1904)
    - General
      - 1943 (Box 35, Folder 1905-1907)
      - 1944 (Box 35, Folder 1908-1909)
      - 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1910-1913)
      - 1947 (Box 35, Folder 1914-1915)
  - Armed Forces: Navy and Coast Guard, 1943-1957
    - Coast Guard, 1943-1947 (Box 35, Folder 1916)
    - Marine Corps, 1943-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1917)
    - Navy, 1943-1947, 1957
      - 1943 (Box 35, Folder 1918)
      - 1943 (continued) (Box 36, Folder 1919)
      - 1944 (Box 36, Folder 1920-1921)
      - 1945 (Box 36, Folder 1922-1924)
      - 1946 (Box 36, Folder 1925)
      - 1947 (Box 36, Folder 1926)
      - 1957 (Box 36, Folder 1927)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 1928)
  - Armed Forces: Conscription (includes Selective Service, Universal Military Training), 1943-1964
    - 1943 (Box 36, Folder 1929)
    - 1944 (Box 36, Folder 1930)
    - 1945 (Box 36, Folder 1931-1939)
    - 1946 (Box 36, Folder 1940)
    - 1947 (Box 36, Folder 1941-1944)
    - 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1945-1952)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 1953-1958)
    - 1952-1955 (Box 37, Folder 1959-1961)
    - 1952-1955 (continued) (Box 38, Folder 1962-1966)
    - 1955-1964 (Box 38, Folder 1967-1971)
  - Armed Forces: Allotments and Insurance, 1943-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1972-1974)
  - Armed Forces: National Cemeteries; 1945, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 1975)
  - Armed Forces: Civilian Pilot Training, 1943-1946 (Box 39, Folder 1976-1978)
  - Armed Forces: Demobilization, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 1979-1980)
  - Armed Forces: Demobilization (continued) (Box 40, Folder 1981-1982)
  - Armed Forces: Discharges, 1946-1957 (Box 40, Folder 1983-1984)
  - Armed Forces: Furloughs, 1943-1945 (Box 40, Folder 1985)
  - Armed Forces: Garden Springs Housing, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 1986)
  - Armed Forces: Casualties (includes obituaries and outgoing condolence correspondence)
    - 1943 (Box 40, Folder 1987)
    - 1944 (Box 40, Folder 1988-1989)
    - 1945 (Box 40, Folder 1990-1992)
    - 1950-1953 (Box 40, Folder 1993)
  - Armed Forces: Office of War Information, 1943-1945 (Box 41, Folder 1994)
  - Armed Forces: Commissions (Nurses), 1943-1945 (Box 41, Folder 1995)
  - Armed Forces: Commissions, 1943-1948 (Box 41, Folder 1996-1997)
  - Armed Forces: Pearl Harbor, 1942-1944 (Box 41, Folder 1998)
  - Armed Forces: Postwar Problems
    - 1943 (Box 41, Folder 1999-2001)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 2002-2005)
  - Armed Forces: Prisoner of war camps (domestic), 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 2006)
  - Armed Forces: Prisoners of war
    - 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 2007)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 42, Folder 2008)
  - Armed Forces: Releases, 1943-1948 (Box 42, Folder 2009-2014)
  - Armed Forces: Reserves
    - 1947 (Box 42, Folder 2015)
    - 1948 (Box 42, Folder 2016)
  - Armed Forces: Soldiers' Vote, 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 2017-2018)
  - Armed Forces: Transfers, 1943-1948 (Box 43, Folder 2019-2020)
  - Armed Forces: War claims, 1943-1945 (Box 43, Folder 2021)
  - Bureau of Standards, 1948-1952 (Box 43, Folder 2022)
  - Civil Service
    - 1943 (Box 43, Folder 2023-2024)
    - 1944 (Box 43, Folder 2025-2026)
    - 1945 (Box 43, Folder 2027-2033)
    - 1945 (continued) (Box 44, Folder 2034-2035)
    - 1947 (Box 44, Folder 2036-2040)
    - 1948 (Box 44, Folder 2041-2044)
    - 1949 (Box 45, Folder 2045-2046)
    - 1950 (Box 45, Folder 2047)
    - 1951 (Box 45, Folder 2048-2049)
    - 1952 (Box 45, Folder 2050-2051)
    - 1953 (Box 45, Folder 2052-2053)
    - 1954 (Box 45, Folder 2054-2057)
    - 1955 (Box 46, Folder 2058-2060)
    - 1956 (Box 46, Folder 2061-2063)
    - 1957 (Box 46, Folder 2064-2065)
    - 1958 (Box 46, Folder 2066-2068)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 47, Folder 2069)
    - 1959 (Box 47, Folder 2070-2073)
    - 1960 (Box 47, Folder 2074-2075)
    - 1961 (Box 47, Folder 2076-2077)
    - 1962 (Box 47, Folder 2078-2079)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 48, Folder 2080-2082)
    - 1963 (Box 48, Folder 2083-2085)
    - 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2086-2092)
  - Columbia Interstate Commission
    - 1945-1949 (Box 49, Folder 2093-2101)
    - 1945-1949 (continued) (Box 50, Folder 2102-2103)
    - 1950-1960 (Box 50, Folder 2104-2108)
    - Grand Coulee Dam photographs; 1946, undated (Box 50, Folder 2109)
  - Columbia Valley Authority
    - 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 2110-2111)
    - 1945-1946 (continued) (Box 51, Folder 2112-2118)
    - 1947-1950 (Box 51, Folder 2119-2120)
    - 1947-1950 (continued) (Box 52, Folder 2121-2123)
  - Commerce Department, 1947-1955 (Box 52, Folder 2124-2127)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation; 1943, 1950-1958 (Box 52, Folder 2128-2131)
  - District of Columbia, 1941-1952 (Topics include: public welfare, budget appropriations, housing, taxation, Metropolitan Police Department, fire department, public schools, National Capital Sesquicentennial, home rule)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 53, Folder 2132)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 53, Folder 2133)
    - 1943-1947 (Box 53, Folder 2134)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 53, Folder 2135)
    - 1942-1947 (Box 53, Folder 2136)
    - 1947 (Box 53, Folder 2137)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 53, Folder 2138)
    - 1940-1948 (Box 53, Folder 2139)
    - 1947 (Box 54, Folder 2140)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 2141)
    - 1947 (Box 54, Folder 2142-2144)
    - 1940-1947 (Box 54, Folder 2145)
    - 1947 (Box 54, Folder 2146)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 54, Folder 2147)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 55, Folder 2148)
    - 1947 (Box 55, Folder 2149)
    - 1943-1947 (Box 55, Folder 2150)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 55, Folder 2151)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 55, Folder 2152)
    - 1947 (Box 55, Folder 2153-2155)
    - 1947 (continued) (Box 56, Folder 2156-2157)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 56, Folder 2158)
    - 1947 (Box 56, Folder 2159)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 56, Folder 2160)
    - 1943-1948 (Box 56, Folder 2161)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 56, Folder 2162-2163)
    - 1946-1947 (continued) (Box 57, Folder 2164-2165)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 57, Folder 2166-2167)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 57, Folder 2168)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 57, Folder 2169)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 57, Folder 2170)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 57, Folder 2171)
  - Education (Office of), 1941-1952
    - 1948 (Box 58, Folder 2172-2173)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 58, Folder 2174)
    - 1944 (Box 58, Folder 2175-2176)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 2177-2179)
    - 1949 (Box 59, Folder 2180-2187)
    - 1950 (Box 60, Folder 2188)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 2189)
    - 1951-1954 (Box 60, Folder 2190)
    - 1955 (Box 60, Folder 2191)
    - 1956 (Box 60, Folder 2192)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 2193)
    - 1958 (Box 61, Folder 2192-2194)
    - 1957 (Box 61, Folder 2195-2197)
    - 1960 (Box 61, Folder 2198-2199)
    - 1960 (continued) (Box 62, Folder 3000-3001)
    - 1959 (Box 62, Folder 3002-3003)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 62, Folder 3004)
    - 1959 (Box 62, Folder 3005)
    - 1961 (Box 63, Folder 3006-3010)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 3011)
    - 1960 (Box 63, Folder 3012-3013)
    - 1961 (Box 64, Folder 3014-3020)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 3021)
    - 1964 (Box 64, Folder 3022)
    - 1964 (continued) (Box 65, Folder 3023)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 65, Folder 3024)
    - 1962 (Box 65, Folder 3025-3029)
    - 1963 (Box 66, Folder 3030-3035)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 66, Folder 3036-3037)
    - 1964 (Box 66, Folder 3038)
    - 1964 (continued) (Box 67, Folder 3039-3044)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 67, Folder 3045)
    - 1962 (Box 67, Folder 3046)
  - Farm Policy Information
    - 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 3047)
    - 1950 (Box 68, Folder 3048-3049)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 3050)
    - 1949 (Box 68, Folder 3051)
  - Farm Forum (Spokane)
    - 1960-1964 (Box 68, Folder 3052)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 3053)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 3054)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 68, Folder 3055)
  - Farm Policy Information
    - 1956 (Box 69, Folder 3056-3059)
    - 1955 (Box 69, Folder 3060-3062)
    - 1954 (Box 69, Folder 3063)
    - 1953 (Box 69, Folder 3064)
    - 1958 (Box 70, Folder 3065-3067)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 3068)
    - 1957 (Box 70, Folder 3069-3071)
  - Farm Security Administration
    - 1943 (Box 71, Folder 3072-3074)
  - Farmers' Home Administration, 1943-1965
    - 1957 (Box 71, Folder 3075)
    - 1956 (Box 71, Folder 3076)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 3077)
    - 1953 (Box 71, Folder 3078)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 3079)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 71, Folder 3080)
    - 1949 (Box 71, Folder 3081)
    - 1946-1948 (Box 71, Folder 3082)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 3083-3084)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 3085)
    - 1958 (Box 72, Folder 3086)
    - 1964 (Box 72, Folder 3087)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 72, Folder 3088)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 3089)
  - Foreign Agriculture Service
    - 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 3090)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 3091)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 73, Folder 3092)
    - 1949 (Box 73, Folder 3093)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 73, Folder 3094)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 73, Folder 3095-3096)
    - 1953 (Box 73, Folder 3097-3098)
    - Photographs (Box 73, Folder 3099)
  - Foreign Agricultural Relations
    - 1955 (Box 74, Folder 3100)
    - 1953-1956 (Box 74, Folder 3101)
    - 1954 (Box 74, Folder 3102)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 74, Folder 3103)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 3104)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 74, Folder 3105)
  - Federal Communications Commission
    - 1961 (Box 75, Folder 3106)
    - 1960 (Box 75, Folder 3107)
    - 1959 (Box 75, Folder 3108)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 3109)
    - 1956 (Box 75, Folder 3110)
    - 1955 (Box 75, Folder 3111)
    - 1954 (Box 75, Folder 3112)
    - 1953 (Box 75, Folder 3113)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 75, Folder 3114)
    - 1952 (Box 75, Folder 3115)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 3116)
    - 1949 (Box 75, Folder 3117)
    - 1943-1947 (Box 75, Folder 3118)
    - 1964 (Box 76, Folder 3119-3120)
    - 1963 (Box 76, Folder 3121-3123)
    - 1962 (Box 76, Folder 3124-3126)
  - Federal Communications Commission: Paid TV
    - 1960 (Box 77, Folder 3127)
    - 1958 (Box 77, Folder 3128)
    - 1958 (Box 77, Folder 3129)
    - 1958 (Box 77, Folder 3130)
  - Federal Communications Commission: Bridgeport
    - 1955 (Box 77, Folder 3131-3134)
    - 1954 (Box 77, Folder 3135-3137)
    - 1960 (Box 78, Folder 3138)
    - 1959 (Box 78, Folder 3139-3140)
    - 1958 (Box 78, Folder 3141)
    - 1959 (Box 78, Folder 3142)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 3143-3144)
    - 1956 (Box 78, Folder 3145-3147)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 3148)
  - Federal Reserve System
    - 1953-1958 (Box 79, Folder 3149)
  - Federal Trade Commission
    - 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 3150)
    - 1953 (Box 79, Folder 3151)
    - 1952 (Box 79, Folder 3152-3153)
    - 1951 (Box 79, Folder 3154-3155)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 3156)
    - 1960, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 3157)
    - 1961 (Box 79, Folder 3158)
    - 1960 (Box 79, Folder 3159)
    - 1959 (Box 79, Folder 3160)
    - 1958 (Box 79, Folder 3161-3162)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 3163)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 3164)
    - 1954 (Box 79, Folder 3165)
  - Forest Service
    - 1950 (Box 80, Folder 3166)
    - 1948 (Box 80, Folder 3167)
    - 1947 (Box 80, Folder 3168-3171)
    - 1946 (Box 80, Folder 3172)
    - 1945 (Box 80, Folder 3173-3174)
    - 1944 (Box 80, Folder 3175-3176)
    - 1943 (Box 80, Folder 3177-3178)
    - 1954 (Box 81, Folder 3179)
    - 1953 (Box 81, Folder 3180-3181)
    - 1952 (Box 81, Folder 3182-3183)
    - 1951 (Box 81, Folder 3184)
    - 1950 (Box 81, Folder 3185)
    - 1949 (Box 81, Folder 3186-3187)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 81, Folder 3188)
    - 1959 (Box 82, Folder 3189)
    - 1958 (Box 82, Folder 3190-3191)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 82, Folder 3192)
    - 1956 (Box 82, Folder 3193-3194)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 3195)
    - 1957 (Box 82, Folder 3196-3199)
    - 1956 (Box 82, Folder 3200-3202)
    - 1955 (Box 82, Folder 3203-3204)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 3205)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 83, Folder 3206)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 3207-3210)
    - 1958 (Box 83, Folder 3211-3214)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 83, Folder 3215)
    - 1960 (Box 84, Folder 3216)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 84, Folder 3217)
    - 1961 (Box 84, Folder 3218-3223)
    - 1960 (Box 84, Folder 3224-3229)
  - Forest Service: Caron Case
    - 1961 (Box 85, Folder 3230-3236)
  - Forest Service
    - 1964 (Box 85, Folder 3237-3238)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 3239)
    - 1962 (Box 85, Folder 3240)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 3241)
    - 1963 (Box 86, Folder 3242-3246)
    - 1962 (Box 86, Folder 3247-3251)
  - General Services Administration
    - 1958 (Box 87, Folder 3252-3253)
    - 1959 (Box 87, Folder 3254-3255)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 3256)
    - 1960 (Box 87, Folder 3257)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 3258)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 3259)
    - 1955 (Box 87, Folder 3260)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 87, Folder 3261)
    - 1953 (Box 87, Folder 3262)
    - 1948-1952 (Box 87, Folder 3263)
    - 1961 (Box 88, Folder 3264)
    - 1961 (Box 88, Folder 3265-3267)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 3268)
    - 1959 (Box 88, Folder 3269-3272)
    - 1964 (Box 88, Folder 3273)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 3274)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 88, Folder 3275)
    - 1963 (Box 88, Folder 3276-3277)
    - 1962 (Box 88, Folder 3278-3280)
  - Health Department
    - 1964 (Box 89, Folder 3281)
    - 1963 (Box 89, Folder 3282)
    - 1962 (Box 89, Folder 3283)
    - 1961 (Box 89, Folder 3284-3285)
    - 1960 (Box 89, Folder 3286)
    - 1959 (Box 89, Folder 3287)
    - 1958 (Box 89, Folder 3288)
    - 1957 (Box 89, Folder 3289-3291)
    - 1956 (Box 89, Folder 3292-3293)
    - 1951-1954 (Box 89, Folder 3294)
    - 1950 (Box 89, Folder 3295)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 89, Folder 3296)
    - 1946-1948 (Box 89, Folder 3297)
  - Health Department: Medicare
    - 1951, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 3298)
    - 1950 (Box 90, Folder 3299-3300)
    - 1949 (Box 90, Folder 3301-3309)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 90, Folder 3310)
    - 1945 (Box 90, Folder 3311)
    - 1944 (Box 90, Folder 3312)
    - 1943 (Box 90, Folder 3313-3315)
    - 1961 (Box 91, Folder 3316-3322)
    - 1960 (Box 91, Folder 3323-3333)
    - 1962 (Box 92, Folder 3334-3349)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 93, Folder 3350-3363)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 94, Folder 3364-3373)
    - 1964 (Box 95, Folder 3374-3378)
    - 1963 (Box 95, Folder 3379)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 3380)
    - 1964 (Box 95, Folder 3381)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 95, Folder 3382-3383)
    - 1963 (Box 95, Folder 3384-3387)
  - Health Department: Hospitals
    - 1964 (Box 96, Folder 3388)
    - 1963 (Box 96, Folder 3389)
    - 1964 (Box 96, Folder 3390)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 96, Folder 3391)
    - 1960 (Box 96, Folder 3392)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 96, Folder 3393)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 96, Folder 3394)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 96, Folder 3395)
    - 1952 (Box 96, Folder 3396)
    - 1951 (Box 96, Folder 3397)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 3398)
    - 1949 (Box 96, Folder 3399)
    - 1945 (Box 96, Folder 3400)
    - 1944 (Box 96, Folder 3401-3402)
  - Hoover Commission
    - 1949 (Box 97, Folder 3403-3404)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 97, Folder 3405)
    - 1956 (Box 97, Folder 3406)
    - 1952 (Box 97, Folder 3407)
    - 1951 (Box 97, Folder 3408)
    - 1950 (Box 97, Folder 3409-3415)
    - 1950 (continued) (Box 98, Folder 3416-3418)
    - 1949 (Box 98, Folder 3419-3420)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 3421)
    - 1957 (Box 98, Folder 3422-3424)
  - Hoover Commission: Corruption in Government
    - 1951-1952 (Box 98, Folder 3425)
  - Internal Revenue Service
    - 1956 (Box 99, Folder 3426-3427)
    - 1955 (Box 99, Folder 3428)
    - 1954 (Box 99, Folder 3429)
    - 1953 (Box 99, Folder 3430-3431)
    - 1952 (Box 99, Folder 3432)
    - 1951 (Box 99, Folder 3433)
    - 1950 (Box 99, Folder 3434)
    - 1949 (Box 99, Folder 3435-3437)
    - 1948 (Box 99, Folder 3438)
    - 1943 (Box 99, Folder 3439-3443)
    - 1962 (Box 100, Folder 3444-3445)
    - 1961 (Box 100, Folder 3447-3448)
    - 1960 (Box 100, Folder 3449)
    - 1959 (Box 100, Folder 3450-3451)
    - 1958 (Box 100, Folder 3452-3455)
    - 1957 (Box 100, Folder 3456)
    - 1964 (Box 101, Folder 3457-3460)
    - 1963 (Box 101, Folder 3461-3464)
    - 1962 (Box 101, Folder 3465)
    - 1961 (Box 101, Folder 3466)
    - 1960 (Box 101, Folder 3467)
    - 1957 (Box 101, Folder 3468-3470)
    - 1956 (Box 101, Folder 3471-3472)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - 1950 (Box 102, Folder 3473)
    - 1949 (Box 102, Folder 3474-3476)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 102, Folder 3477)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 102, Folder 3478)
    - 1951 (Box 102, Folder 3479-3480)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 3481)
    - 1951 (Box 102, Folder 3481-3482)
    - 1951 (continued) (Box 103, Folder 3483-3485)
    - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 3486-3489)
    - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 3490)
    - 1958 (Box 103, Folder 3491)
    - 1957 (Box 103, Folder 3492-3493)
    - 1956 (Box 103, Folder 3494-3495)
    - 1955 (Box 103, Folder 3496-3497)
    - 1954 (Box 104, Folder 3498)
    - 1953 (Box 104, Folder 3499-3500)
    - 1952 (Box 104, Folder 3501-3502)
    - 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3503-3509)
    - 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3510-3519)
    - 1964 (Box 106, Folder 3520)
    - 1963 (Box 106, Folder 3521-3531)
    - 1962 (Box 106, Folder 3532-3534)
  - Justice Department: Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - 1950-1064 (Box 107, Folder 3535)
  - Justice Department
    - 1963-1964 (Box 107, Folder 3536)
    - 1962 (Box 107, Folder 3537)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 107, Folder 3538)
    - 1959 (Box 107, Folder 3539)
    - 1958 (Box 107, Folder 3540)
    - 1957 (Box 107, Folder 3541)
    - 1955 (Box 107, Folder 3542)
    - 1952 (Box 107, Folder 3543)
    - 1951 (Box 107, Folder 3544)
    - 1950 (Box 107, Folder 3545)
    - 1948 (Box 107, Folder 3546)
    - 1947 (Box 107, Folder 3547)
  - Library of Congress
    - 1957 (Box 108, Folder 3548)
    - 1964 (Box 108, Folder 3549)
    - 1963 (Box 108, Folder 3550)
    - 1960 (Box 108, Folder 3551)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 108, Folder 3552)
    - 1959 (Box 108, Folder 3553)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 108, Folder 3554)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 108, Folder 3555)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 108, Folder 3556)
  - National Defense (Department of): Legislation
    - 1964 (Box 108, Folder 3557)
    - 1963 (Box 108, Folder 3558-3562)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 108, Folder 3563)
    - 1959 (Box 108, Folder 3564)
    - 1958 (Box 108, Folder 3565-3566)
    - 1955 (Box 109, Folder 3567)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 109, Folder 3568)
    - 1953 (Box 109, Folder 3569)
    - 1957 (Box 109, Folder 3570)
    - 1953-1956 (Box 109, Folder 3571)
    - 1952 (Box 109, Folder 3572)
    - 1951 (Box 109, Folder 3573-3576)
    - 1950 (Box 109, Folder 3577-3580)
    - 1949 (Box 109, Folder 3581-3582)
    - 1948 (Box 109, Folder 3583)
  - National Defense (Department of): Personal, A-G, 1948-1951
    - 1951: A (Box 110, Folder 3584)
    - 1949-1950: A (Box 110, Folder 3585)
    - 1951: B (Box 110, Folder 3586-3587)
    - 1950: B (Box 110, Folder 3588)
    - 1948-1949: B (Box 110, Folder 3589)
    - 1951: C (Box 110, Folder 3590-3592)
    - 1950: C (Box 110, Folder 3593)
    - 1951: D (Box 110, Folder 3594)
    - 1950: D (Box 110, Folder 3595)
    - 1951: F (Box 110, Folder 3596)
    - 1951: G (Box 110, Folder 3597)
    - 1950: G (Box 110, Folder 3598)
    - 1949: G (Box 110, Folder 3599)
    - 1947-1949: G (Box 110, Folder 3600)
  - National Defense (Department of): Personal, H-R, 1948-1951
    - 1949-1950: MISC (Box 111, Folder 3601)
    - 1951: H (Box 111, Folder 3602-3603)
    - 1949-1950: H (Box 111, Folder 3604)
    - 1950-1951: I (Box 111, Folder 3605)
    - 1951: K (Box 111, Folder 3606)
    - 1949-1950: K (Box 111, Folder 3607)
    - 1951: L (Box 111, Folder 3608)
    - 1950: L (Box 111, Folder 3609)
    - 1951: M (Box 111, Folder 3610)
    - 1950: M (Box 111, Folder 3611)
    - 1949: M (Box 111, Folder 3612)
    - 1951: N (Box 111, Folder 3613)
    - 1950: N (Box 111, Folder 3614)
    - 1951: O (Box 111, Folder 3615)
    - 1948-1951: P (Box 111, Folder 3616)
    - 1951: R (Box 111, Folder 3617-3618)
    - 1950: R (Box 111, Folder 3619)
  - National Defense (Department of): Personal, S-Z, 1948-1951
    - 1951: S (Box 112, Folder 3620-3622)
    - 1949-1950: S (Box 112, Folder 3623)
    - 1951: T (Box 112, Folder 3624)
    - 1950: T (Box 112, Folder 3625)
    - 1949-1951: U-Z (Box 112, Folder 3626)
  - National Defense (Department of): Personal, A-L, 1952-1954
    - 1953-1954: A-B (Box 112, Folder 3627)
    - 1953: B (Box 112, Folder 3628)
    - 1952: B (Box 112, Folder 3629)
    - 1953-1954: C (Box 112, Folder 3630)
    - 1952: C (Box 112, Folder 3631)
    - 1953-1954: D (Box 112, Folder 3632)
    - 1952: D (Box 112, Folder 3633)
    - 1953-1954: E (Box 112, Folder 3634)
    - 1953-1954: F (Box 112, Folder 3635)
    - 1952: F (Box 112, Folder 3636)
    - 1953-1954: G (Box 112, Folder 3637)
    - 1952: G (Box 112, Folder 3638)
    - 1954: H (Box 113, Folder 3639)
    - 1953: H (Box 113, Folder 3640)
    - 1952: H (Box 113, Folder 3641)
    - 1953: I (Box 113, Folder 3642)
    - 1952-1953: J (Box 113, Folder 3643)
    - 1953: K (Box 113, Folder 3644)
    - 1952: K (Box 113, Folder 3645)
    - 1954: L (Box 113, Folder 3646)
    - 1953: L (Box 113, Folder 3647)
    - 1952: L (Box 113, Folder 3648)
  - National Defense (Department of): Personal, M-Z, 1952-1954
    - 1954: M (Box 113, Folder 3649)
    - 1952-1953: M (Box 113, Folder 3650)
    - 1952-1953: M (Box 113, Folder 3651)
    - 1953-1954: N (Box 113, Folder 3652)
    - 1952-1953: O (Box 113, Folder 3653)
    - 1952-1954: P (Box 113, Folder 3654)
    - 1953-1954: R (Box 113, Folder 3655)
    - 1952: R (Box 113, Folder 3656)
    - 1954: S (Box 114, Folder 3657)
    - 1953: S (Box 114, Folder 3658-3660)
    - 1952: S (Box 114, Folder 3661)
    - 1952-1954: T (Box 114, Folder 3662)